Oh.
OK on your own. The four
years ago that they were.
Doing.
OK. But the. Way that it did. It.
Was the strangest time but. Which is
why I didn't crash out like always and
what you're expected to
do. Nice. All yours.
Are. Everything with. The I.R.S.
Well let. Me me.
All about it you've done
a good job while I was gone.
And forget. I did Big get
a lot richer when you when
and. Where Rich thanks.
Are forgot to tell you we got
a couple of new spots downtown real class
to get the guy way show you the books I'd
take your word for it might go away.
Because we got troubles to take care that
trouble. Like when we was kid. Main
you know against everybody OK my.
Show. Got my run. When it right thanks to
my art.
Your.
Was.
Little.
And on the planet walking down the street
minding my own business I step off the
curb the car comes here
around the corner against
a red light. The cop should've
picked up the driver that caught me.
On your trusty Yeah how long I've been
in this town three hundred are near.
The top. To front the front
line and I'm. Tired of.
This just. Rock me precisely rock.
The armed present order is caused by. To
this old fool I would just do so you're
a guest of the most common compound
of hydrogen and so. Am I right.
I pose my life to so become. My
young the way. It was I'm thankful.
Rose that chemist. Before the ahem me.
Where there wrote my. YOUNG MAN What is
the last thing you remember before they
brought you.
To contrast. Aware of the political.
Enemy. Right next to me
and he missed he did
miss. Your demo. We're on day.
To day the way it is true only of
a solipsist down. Comes to mind.
The I don't care where I am. I
got yes smiling. When I first
asked expand. Here.
I mean. Look at.
The sort of temperature that. Could
a bus stop it's high
especially the blood of just
a narrow Despina careful to back up anything
but seventy three percent of you are
going to catch my death of cold people. Who
shop conditions I have tickets to Ward
and I have no need of your infant suggestions
I'll attend to this matter most of my
opponent is always
a bit more of his it's my pro-choice this
time it happens to be one judge big part
. Of the New World but we'll
see who goes down to defeat my
beloved stock that policy runs
to be hold. I have lately been
beset by
a great. My interest is working
overtime but superior though he may be
and though he set up
a thousand judge parkas to pull me in must
recognize that I am still master of my
own sphere. That. Once in my command
is their last.
Meeting that they're helping
him. But have no authority or.
Knowledge but if I had
a piece of. Apologize
for you to see the old boy. Omitting.
And angry in the country I am but
a piece. I'm delighted to but his name.
To me to do and sold it was he
a calculated it to the
bank. To think why not.
Ever see that place before. It was just
getting to school and to keep running water
that happens to be
a picture of Judge Frederick
pucca. He looks precisely
they look exactly alike. And this likeness
is just the weapon I need to defeat Mr
Parker. It could go.
On but they want to. Know because I don't
know people I. Think it's just that
little a stick in them
it's way down below in
a way that I don't now.
Know but I'm in this joint.
Back to back.
Nobody doubting you know what if I
did. A breakout from every right.
To it. Or you. Like.
Me That smiling. At you but.
I can now begin to think of somebody I
want to get to you know. To do you.
Good but. In
a. Big. Group.
Well it is. What you get one nice.
Big stream. That kind of. The case might.
You. Find it.
An argument down in time immemorial
what you're talking about
a good education the most liberal one I
only went to grade I went through the whole
gamut of learning I know everything that
I knew so bad but you know when I have
a number of aliases I have
a long record of the name of it's doubly
weak and there are some who claim I'm more
of one nation than another but that's not
true and I'm of all nations no favorites
you look like a con man. Come and
make you marry the young women of
a good way to
a guy with down Lady. And I think my
plan or our daily diet and I didn't like
my lip for me while you may and reckon
not. Deny yourself frame and play is like
a touch and toss the part about you know
my I am so that it makes the most of what
we get
a spin people to into the dock
just. Talking skill. Needed
or wanted for
a laugh. Patient again not knowing about
I never saw no laugh about my old life
time I left school I ran away from home on
a comic books was always from. My life.
I've been doing it trying to be somebody
and I did pretty good but myself up where
I had no money no place to sleep at that
guy and my business friend
a man I. Have to work with that he's.
Allowed to go to take it to get out there.
Moment.
I have to turn it up. For my
tryout for my feet make the
right night not looking to go.
Wow them a just tell a guy down in
a destination but what about for your sort
of I don't feel the first I haven't got
a body bag out nobody home I'm going to
get smiley. You might like it don't know
what hit you until I find your body not
how money I going to find it where I know
everyone has this physical kind of what
is double I have no way your double it I
mean
a guy which looks like me spitting image
I suppose and they don't want to give me
is but you'd be asleep he won't have anything
to say about it what happens when he
wakes up when he wakes up he'll be you.
And your loving you'll be able. To
everyone else will be him of
course just so you'll be so. Good
at it again when I stop whining about it
leave everything to me I mean no con man.
I'm so it is this cold air makes me it
would apply don't like coke climb. It's I
don't feel I've been. And if you know I
got nobody need I've come to feel close
I've been down below so long that even my
soul is going to custom to the heat Hey.
If I got nobody I've got to bring it right
right. Thing is no fingerprints right
right. I can get away with money to not
exactly without fingers you cannot squeeze
the trigger. Right want to squeeze it.
Does it come across as
a saint the way Smiley's are saying the
body we want is. Don't you forget you have
a little job to do for me first that was
a deal. OK. And or an agent.
But the idea of bringing me here I'm going
to go to the fingers to squeeze that
trigger. How do you think I get in
a criminal court how did I figure getting
out of that jam going on but I know what
I did. That was made
this or be you need to
trust me OK Let's go.
And you know see giant. After man I'm with
you there cops and seeds live on mine
they were new to know.
Your honor to defend this case has been
able to establish an alibi the testimony
conclusively proves that this man was at
the scene of the crime and at the exact
time it was committed therefore I respect
fully request the collapse of the law I'm
not going to take any more of this.
But I have a collapsed ID. No judge of
a test out on me. This
court is not just. Going
to do let's go there
go get me no art as I do are
laden get me there city
don't you never forget I'm boss Here's
a day I shouldn't have been
so proves. I've given him
a sedative let him sleep while
I'm getting all. Showed up to.
Where I don't know.
Oh oh do I know where your double was if
this guy down the around St Louis you know
got to stead of me to bend it in as eat
a guy you want to get in line to
do it Yes And yeah I was sent. Out
on
a nice guy Jag iron muscle
and in no Judge's body
what difference does it make to
serve your purpose and mine in
what happens when he gets up and find
hand when we're through with him he won't
know this thing. On
a single. Solitary estate what about you
and you're going to find yourself
a body here I don't care one bit you
for. You know the important point
in going to thank you
and I won't forget it
yeah yeah.
But you don't. Choose in
a day. The part of. She read you
into this man is to you can refuse
him to steal. Relax.
Oh Albert stop this far down here Yes
So she's making coffee or. May I
inquire how to judge it's all good night's
rest to be on top of that skirt. And out
of the druggist where you get the sedative
just in case he wakes up to get stuff
it'll be ready for him he tells me. But
thinks it's nothing serious I
hope Matt. Thanks but. No I
don't think so however I've been expecting
this for some time but he said that one
can only do so much there's going to
Fred's temperament when he made it in the
morning I suggest you find him
into his car and get him away for
a couple of weeks I would judge
a secretary not his wife that remains
in it and you soon will be if it can't
possibly go away now why
would the election only
a few days off the speech of the auditorium
tomorrow about it or is that your own
way I suppose you will know that's not
them that nobody can stop Fred nobody can
push him on I'm the last one to want to
see him hurt or sick you believe that.
Course. I'll bring him to you off the first
thing I'm like oh no. I wouldn't do it
all. Not all people are ready
to accept psychiatry as
a normal branch of medicine the
general impression is I believe that
a man who needs
a psychiatrist must be crazy. Ridiculous
of course but they are and some people are
rather reluctant to cast their votes for
lunatics if I hadn't noticed the debate if
I came here fiber about it.
Albert. Yes this driver
I'm going home with
a judge awakened during the
night please go yes to stop.
Dad these pointless but
nine shot kids get on it.
I aged to wake you say you
were sleeping so peacefully
today I gotta one what's it.
You got onto I hope so said. I can
feel myself I'm solid Some I'd
like to be you quite alright
say alright sure I'm
alright but. Pleasant.
Day and
a quiet OK. I. Didn't
explain here till I think I don't probably
was in your bed and that I don't like
being. Who you are anyway really I got to
tell you know I say flat out I'm not but
your man said and if you're part of me your
back is ready you said I don't need no
bad they cleaned me out good when they let
me out wedges I'm big on bass dad did
rags close close
a good job I did I got to get dressed and
get this time going away. One of my judge
or an undertaker and you don't know what
fancy stripes and fancy stripes. Never in
line know what I want to dance. Right
Democrats said. Time and time again.
You watch it what are you going
to do help you into this and the.
Return of Iraq yes.
It will be stabbed this
is out I I don't wish to
a lab you but the judge is definitely not
himself that's why I'm terribly worried
about all that would be splendid
and to hurry Peace thank you.
If you. Get me a ticket on a next plane
a thing knowing the bus when you realize
your work you don't really care for
a good many years get it but your appointment
to an appointment at St Lloyd which
comes first but plain reservations are
hard to get this especially on such short
notice OK and call your pride and get me
a special plane off myself. Need
some dough is there any around the usual
places don't give me no doubletalk where
the dough kinda saved. I don't see no say
if I seem to be baffling I'll shut up
until I had said it was
a stronger behind the pictures of the
flock of pictures the one with the boat.
The butt.
And the sandpaper.
Have you forgotten the combination I
don't know the nation this is death.
Please OK wait in there is hardship
you can't possibly town to date her.
It's.
Not
a way to. Truth. And that would
explain my actions. That explain to me I
don't like the surprise I've been in the
surprises store for you if you try to run
out on me again I read it out on not.
Just happen out of St though it together
correct that Brad can wait comes first.
Thing up so I makes me I'm
comfortable. And happy. And
I oppose out into. QUESTION That engine
trouble sir will have to go back
to the feel. Strange coincidence.
That my. Father died first.
I'm sure he said thank
you and yes Mr. Lewis I
can't imagine what could take him in. Time
for the seven things to do you should
have done something else for me or let's
talk to my son I tried to his property but
he gave me a portion I'll keep
it's test ridiculous the judge
a gentility itself he never pushed anybody
he never did any of the things he did
this morning from the first time he
awakened he acted peculiarly. Go
along when I went to help him dress
he is he told me to scram. If she
had said. That was the very word to
use Miss Barbara. You're certain
you want having hallucinations out there I
only wish that were true it's been most
disturbing I would have called Dr Higgins
but I didn't have the opportunity to
Narconon now that I'm going to speak.
How doctor he can be as Barbara Foster Not
a word to anybody else or if the scope is
problematic because I'm afraid not only
of the air he took
a plane for St Louis. But
it's extraordinary. Well.
Be unduly alarmed it may be only
a passing operation. To see when he gets
back that we know the moment. And let me
warn you Barbara no matter how strange the
don't antagonize him. You may have been
dodging. Perhaps. I understand it's rather
important thing is patient
kind of down that.
Well now they're. Going to be very
patient when. We witness but.
Remember. Not
a word to us so. Got
on it did you would miss your
place Yeah how do is it.
Janet just that. One thing
I was so worried about.
Losing. Your fiance. I'm going
to print all of the judge's go
ahead to make the most of it
you don't realize. This is OK
with any attorney guy going to school
a lot of you never talk like
that before. You. Dive in
yeah. That's bad. Plenty of
careers and all in the right place it's a
bank he doesn't even have to be afraid
a man. May need to step
in at and it's been
a long time he's pretty. Spread ill fated
that the judges had of him Who
are you talking to the next oh
Nick baited.
Him Yes. Did you ever talk to Allen I
know what I NEVER GOING TO BE ALLOWED TO
thing again never seen
a judge do you better get used
to it you know I'll tie Oh red
just. Playing hard to get their
boots what Joe Fine saw here to
own it what's your name oh really Fred
what's your name and I You certainly know my
name I wouldn't accept I know it's
our call your reality rather be.
Hello number I used to run around
like it's just like you. Got
my relaxed I got you
a bad guy right now stop it Fred. I'm
sorry it's OK. To be late.
I've got lots of time of
course but you do have the all the time
to deliver your speech come again your
speech dear it's getting late I do on my
speech and with my ride I want you to
marry the speech you do on behind you wish
for ninety year old part of the plan.
Thank God don't know too much prior to
contact and talk to God Maybe it would be
best to be postponed part
of a batch of I got to make
a speech and make it but it was smal
but it's OK I have to go to take
a few days rest I'll call the campaign
committee and explain to him and watch him
and think I can do what I know you can on
your own and. I can do anything I put my
mind cos I want to go
the auditorium I'm not.
Going to give it to him good.
From our next guest who will make
a con man I am very.
Sorry we had been forgotten by
a lady like black I don't. Pocket
collapse on bad now wait too bad.
And this is this is a Tory. We leave
the helm of our ship in the hands of
a man who spends ago condition is in
question now in the stormy is period in our
state's history. And it's patriotic
citizens we got to do something about the
situation now back in St Louis never mind
St Louis shaggy whatever you did in your
hometown we'll do it better here the
point is we've got to see that the judge
basically we get to see this condition
maybe even gets worse. That's the idea and
we've got the judge hanging on the rope
now we've got to deliver the case. All of
which is only to protect the people like
you now with our boy people can go about
their business in the pursuit of happiness
which is coming to them without Sure
without worry that's right I was speaking
at the auditorium and to give you plenty
of time but on
a good show shaggy one more came in like
he had in court yesterday and will be
dusting off the governor's chair
Farai Boortz My voice of us. And oh
hello. My wife go ahead and remember that
I want to hear that the judge is taking
a turn for the worst will
bring back to State couple.
Imagine me running for governor down here
too modest Come on let's go on and let
them in the room I want to taste
a joint project. Between
A. Lot of.
What he got back which put stick close to
get me to always remember that old there
is is there no excuse me. Please
don't have. It all ready to
start
a weekend that I'm way. Twenty. Years
someone with their talent
I'm sure we can find him
a sequel that would be fine you don't die
thank everyone at least I didn't think
that helping with the worry
you had just been trying to.
Air
getting
a little worried about. Shows
you're on the. Way.
Yeah no it's that's it's
a half hour hour morning burst. Upon
their phones. To say I am against them
because of who they are
because our social event.
And I rank confound when you're
on the first Ankiel it's.
Roster to the day.
He. Why.
Thank you to them thank you
last time and thank you.
Fellow Americans as
a campaign for governor of this great
state goes into its final phase is it an
honor and
a privilege to speak once again and behalf
of the candidate of the citizens better
government committed Judge
Frederick Potter add.
Air.
All kinds raise all those are famous Parker
Youth Foundation created by our again
today ten years ago this one
are going to raise him as
a result show no props ninety
seven per cent sensible right.
Because Judge Parker is
a man who understands the job at all
and I'm going to say this is not
a matter of bad boys and
good boys but rather
a matter of bad conditions and
bug conditions is a man or
a THERE DONE llama by his friends respected
and feared by his enemies I'm out of
countless virtues.
Ladies and gentlemen as we have just
seen why no judge Barker's numerous but
actress modesty. That's the idea let me
down and I'm not letting you down I promise
not about this right away go out there
and tell them off tell them when I say
show me how do you get these people sent
to the prison if they are enemies as I
wish I was not alone OK H.-O.
Always think you. Can tell them what you
think. You know not of and if I don't know
them go out there and give it to them call
them by their right name call them every
name you can think of my bread toilet or
drawers the next governor of this great
state got.
All
right. All right.
All right.
That's all right you. Can Have It stank.
So you know.
You should have just.
Said all.
Of it every day of. Places.
To take it take it to do.
It so to that I'll put this job now but I'm
going to. Just make it here on the job
why don't I just say I'm
a. Yes
. I'd rather you.
Know I don't need that now this chemical.
Drilling the true reason. Sure you and
I do it to the world Sure
sure. You just. Need
to keep him the Jets don't want to
just. Go right ahead you want to.
Hey. What is Negroponte Never mind now
do you believe in well you would look.
For others that you cannot accept advantages
quickly yes prescribed downing you
were magnificent but you know you would
cut out the backed out of Thank You know
somebody who could have done it better
I know dear but I'm afraid of the
aftereffects I know you're going to be if
you never been taken my life but you were
just I'm glad mechanic.
Let's go over you. But
they take their junk out of here give me
a drink the mineral water as I said
I'd drink bourbon you don't do me you
just watch me and some to God Think you
can smoke and drink you know that are you
kidding when you start an apple
Oh yes darling please do
not only make yourself feel
wired in Rose a good and
a bad some smooching.
Darling you had to say.
I. Want to shout I wish you wouldn't do
you had enough excitement for one day.
Static take a pout take
a powder say Oh you mean scratch.
It lad run
a it carefully it I can do to show. That's
funny I never joke.
About eight catalogs that by
any. How do I have to have
a put on the big. I and leave the.
Good I've got to get
home via home. You know
perfectly well I don't live in.
The Jesuits this crew is Jim
you know you guys don't really. I'm
going home in a single bed when I'm in
a way. That I told you.
I was. Thinking about when I have.
This problem what I thought.
Don't I just packed up.
A Let's say I did get back in your cab or
up like you are getting more dire. Than
my relatives picked this up.
In
a closet Yes ma'am. I
have
a son affidavit from depositions of witnesses
in Chicago that came in there was money
why didn't I just watch all this about
Chicago should be critical when you do you
understand your book unpalatable
a couple nights but. I lay. Whose money I
don't see is known in the document and I
finished it on the only place
you'll find his name of the on
a tombstone. Or what is he to do
with a bunch of TAR I don't know
a Bentley all I know and literally securing
in court today right here I'll be there
if you're not like go a parka you be
sure you don't bungle it yeah I know
a lot about trials so do you. Are
you talking the tabbed out of
A.B.R.I.
Probably you want to get Carol sorry your
honor if you're looking to read I was
talking about the hidden
heap of it that's an O.E.M.
Handle at my way place come to bed late
and come that bank Lloyd to face come
across and backstab. I'll show you
a few tricks and how to get Smiley kicks
in never even dreamed of shit you know I
go to with
a trial and that and last and only showed
up to St Louis what are we doing for the
newest year. Just. Not not me.
If I can be when you talk like that and
especially between man smiling. And I got
together. On
a vacation to Florida. It's
a hundred times harder.
For us I tell you themselves than
a song worried I'm get this he said he's
going to rush to the child and how quick
this is going gets. It's dangerous
Tucker a judge in a good recovery
a candidate to make sure you write
a positive going to double
crossing backstage was running
a racket with the judges dope I direct
him. Always wear it the honorable Joe just
put himself right out of the running shaggy
that hunk us was right this judge that
only looks like Eddie he's the biggest two
timing double crossing candidate that
ever ran for office he's even worse than
our enemy. You call him the judge I'm
calling smiley. It looks
like what they put on
a guy was given and they thought it jamming
the rap on eventually attempted murder
this is Benji and husband tried to kill her
father and collect his insurance. They
pushed him in front of
a subway train but they bungled it for the
old man to live with some of the entire
country shocked by the ugliness of it
somehow they fail to see the beauty of what
Chad they get just parka. And they wouldn't
spend all that money trying to square
things before coming up for trial they try
to get the Jets play. They wouldn't do
that. They know it's
impossible to fix judge.
A who's pregnant deal
a man known as Big Headed What's his last
name I can look up no big area I want to
call him up and have him come here quick
before the trial he's too soft for that on
my land no. Well you just
spring for two for two
guy Joe little telegraphic and special
always showing up again big boy.
I have to dish out pie I don't myself when
I put in effect. My chance to get some
of it back. Twenty five grand and
nothing thanks like that this is
why I said Tammas the whole country
is aroused by the whole country
but your honor as is the case of the
people versus Mitchell when eight six nine
four two I can
a case of the people watching Mitchell
one hundred six million or one forty two
they got to yeah you
know I. Know your honor
but if you will only be reasonable let
me bring the Bentleys in. Chakan have
witnesses on the facts say no your honor I
just just want you to see them and have
them say
a word in there all the way
but that desk face. Your
Honor this is Mr or Mrs but they will tell
you that this whole affair was merely
the result of
a tragic misunderstanding this fine upstanding
citizen and this frail innocent law
abiding little lady were simply victims
of circumstance the result of which Mrs
Bentley has been under
the constant care of
a physician she's lost
weight she's been unable to.
Be.
More that can be.
Pumped. You can link learn to get hooked
up with this learn did you do your own
look at it over and over you know shut
up till. Then tips to Kansas City to see
a poor old. And you know get
hold of it out this was him.
To Tammy's playing around with him all
the time. But I got you now let's try
a stats I talked about that you had to get
a workout start telling him away but get.
The run of the court is ready to go you
can't fix this rat from
a nap or I don't want to countries there
are they trying to bribe you imagine when
I tell the story the pressure on this your
sense of self in the governor's chair.
Going to never see Cerda me I'm
sorry are you who you are mitigated
this move. If you had
a body part. The thing
you're going to do that
trick. You should be if he's
gotten away with somebody I don't
know anymore why does it
matter what happened. It isn't
a simple diagnostic case of me. Could be
a throwback to his formative years young
years the boy years and he lived in the
slums effect caused. Fear probably of.
Well maybe
a fate of the high offices running for
being elected to the responsibility that
might mean fate of loving a woman like you
a woman like me. Barbara. I think said
to withdraw from the campaign are
you listening but you can't be this good
as elected right now as I know. You'll be
our you've got to do you've got
to be governor. Judges secretary
of the governor's wife. My
mother. Barbara. We've been
friends for
a long time. I love this girl I've ever
known they're also the most ambitious.
They are not of the kind I don't know much
about neurotic condition but I do know
the but for doing too much to the car
he won't give a lot of poor kids
a chance to grow up like the can do in the
front pocket will. Because he won't wipe
out the dishes on that one but the intro
to Governor park. And this ambitious wench
Barbara Fox is going to
happen to. Try to. Get I was
mistaken forgive me I'm sorry to I'm
sorry that I'm Alex said had to pay for
a living hell. But. After
the workout medivac this
condition may have to put the the team.
There must be handled with patience and
understanding. Going to be difficult for
you nothing difficult where folks can say
if you could possibly get him away for
a short while it would help
anonymously undermine the good.
Friends of Christ our combined.
Love to go ahead and make
the most of it she or you.
Jamie Tonight reality why send
voice over said In addition
Miley you've been negotiated operate nice
the same as in St Louis which is OK with
me and the boys on set and good in reasonable
condition to cope I get conditions to
show when I can have any I get about
percentages only one question. At
a keg What about him Well now
that he's out free again
very early in around anymore yes he was
bumped up the minute he graduated Cali.
What do you know. That means you are
now nobody you know you are operating
alone you don't experience nobody about
nothing or very good bad you wouldn't be
holding out any important information on
as would use planning such as for instance
for instance like silent you know someone
we have been political circles it's maybe
getting
a cut out of everything I told you I
operate strictly alone we had different.
We got it straight smiley there and it
straight from me. Yours truly Smiley
when. You say so. After all if you
weren't exactly telling us the
truth to be complications would somebody
to get it it's always the other guy gets
hurt. Not so good the judges have of course
at the birth of just couldn't figure
out that it was family I just had
a thought before you open up the guy you
got to see if he gives you the OK then
we'll do business be the jews good
that you. Give me his name and then.
You better call on him
right away. Because not
a whole. White. But
yeah yeah very Parker but
a bigot not over the. Pacific Jews
running for governor do. Upright
Yeah I bet you would be if the task that
lies to me would be how you come out by
finding.
My true or my truth and
you belong to the one.
Who. Got it man this
is where we're really.
Really going and where. You.
Have to just. Signing and you.
Are member down upon the.
Location and the room in
the garden. Come and go up
be seated.
Peppina. Now we're on our porch.
On dog and along tonight.
After dinner in the evening
piece. That's going to have.
To wait
a minute we have to
open the door. They're.
Not it may. Be forgot to close the door.
When we're married I'm going to insist
that you can you across the
street. With your marriage.
So it's
a room with you it won't be that big.
Now but here's your step. Ladder
so I could move. There are the pictures of
all the great men of our little tour of
politics I never hear about
a window to be on the. Launching tippy
tippy top down and read what I want to do
on
a radio with you on the. Bridge. At
the night because of the Fed. On
a night and don't want to. Send to me and
that's the most important coming. Out of
the kitchen. And there's.
You mean. One of the it would make him. At
kids. On
a porch of course to. Look
at. Him and make. There.
Are to see and. Like to.
See no difference. Is that matter.
Because those who know this. People
calling me around and smile.
Kids make an assault on
me and. I haven't had. A
new. Attack at you are all you have me.
And. I get that. I think you get much.
Don't see those things because not you
do promise to debut the pounds to get on
about the cool of the election everything.
Let's just enjoy it.
I big problem but perhaps you did prefer
to come back tomorrow Evidently his armor
is on the board to be to date. A way yes.
Happy down there. To what. I have
a mosquito net and on my life.
Back you could say trying.
To make myself. Except maybe
because I found someone other.
Than I want to hold on
to. A place like this.
You.
It's true I know you never make me
so happy to hear you talk like that.
But I'm going to find you.
On mixed.
C.X. . I made
a deal. But how could I know that
you took the good action to. Cut
my arm off and next.
Person look out. For couple
minutes. Max. It's time.
To.
That was
a very touching scene. But if you come
chill in around town I have some nice news
for you. Remember I promised that if you
would help me get Judge Barker and help
you get smiley. But I have to keep my
word even though some others do I did
everything actually who owned the liberty
to. Their burning Judge Parker You made
it more popular at fights in the auditorium
refusing to bribe in the benthic is
this event tested billing and cooing. I
can change carry over to where it is.
Too late for their. Side to
fail I was interrupted to kill
a dish. Or I when I came to
tell you is this. Smiley is in
town. With you to. Come to extend his
cafe business we're going to open up in
this city. But they are money money you
went to jail for. The money killed you.
Get direct counseling. More or
really yeah you are going to suffer
What's more you are getting you know.
Much never save take the program run by
cutting out your in the bargain.
And I. Can't leave Rosie.
Smiley in town is not only
a threat to you but to
Barbara. In the. Mean
. OK Listen dangerous mining figured out
if you're scared. But he sees your refutal
get him he'll get your like you
did before. But this one is free.
You know what that put me into Judge Clark.
Who is body and where would that leave
. Her See. Either way. As
a. Mistake of it her children
she may have. Got to kill it.
And got
a way of putting things which make sense
I don't hear Sadly I know that. I should
probably advice but like you
say. Funny people do and.
Iraq. Are beginning to
see straight and fairly.
Regular. Joe Average.
And. I got
a ten or something something very
important. To use your car my car.
Keys our right if you want to. I want you.
To come here. I want to shit spank me out
of something I'll try to do if I can if
we was already married and have
a nice house at it. And one day
a big rock from
a person came out of his home and
shoulders. And went for kits trucks which.
Because I think you do but this time.
You. Used to speak.
What they. Could not ask
what good life whether.
It had been up in your face. Please permit
for the privilege of expressing my happy
frame of mind and with you facial rentals.
Really has the potential. Of God I don't
put some rancor Sagna the statement.
It's a matter I wouldn't speak
I didn't say your words I see
a driver's license. Left and left of
my other suit in this state that ain't good
about your owner's license. Then I met
your fiance is. Telling
me about a dude to go to
a campaign meeting with you know making
a speech going to recognize me
I'm just proud to amount of
a governor in the next state as a political
shindigs dad tonight and I'm making
a speech is my finances see if you just let
me out of the and my kids want to name
Barbara Foster That's an
interesting set of circumstances
a girl by that name
called the police report
a car stolen and the description of the car
and the license number was identical to
the one you're driving I'm
telling you you're making
a mistake that's what they all say and
how you can explain it down the station
follow me.
You know this should convince your conclusively
I do that I am the only friend you
have first your best smile
a double cross if you want out of this get
it and so the cop pulled up in front of
the girl it had nothing to
do with a race folks being
a she knew you would out to kill which
meant you wouldn't be got ready she'd want
to be you think God knows why Yeah rather
liar mankind has been beset by women
since Adam and Barbara is that true I
should have my grandma that you are batting
where you were last time to see that I
am the only person you can trust not
a fighter they're not
going to try to build in
a spot for having I mean we're not going
to fabricate my head how you it's not.
Fair watch what you have
for your talk and nobody.
Just writes my speech
in the world company of
a room that ladies here is the owner of
a car. Barbara. Barbara
tell us comparable I
am I beg your pardon. I say
this do you know this man
I've never seen before in my life.
Please come to the east you have to file
a complaint with the harbor when I
talk to you alone just just for
a few minutes. This may mean
everything to you to your future
please.
But are. There certain things I can
take because I know you won't believe
but you've got to believe this for the
first time I can remember I'm trying to do
something for somebody else without camera
happens to me I was beginning to change
my stance. Explain don't let me
down here I'm sick sick and kids
which is going to sleep tonight nice
or you would tell me about it you said
something about making you keep.
All right I want you to make
a deal with me I'll get you out
of here if you'll go with me to
a minister and marry but I. Forgot
our bit and your finish were
to start it up to build. Back.
On that you.
Never gone around direct going
in the right direction.
And he said in another place if anyone
offended run of that we believe in me. For
him.
For the party brought. It for Beth. Anyone
a fan if you want to fan one of the
week over leaving me. That. Well
we're going to get married. Why
too many people are getting married these
days without asking themselves why
there's an idea make a note of that or
a sentiment yes dear my husband is to
parent his sermon you'd be right with you
were just the down one then the one who we
could all believe in me it worked better
for getting the millstone were hanging
about his neck and they were cast into the
sea. And he said in another place if I
hadn't offend they cut it off better for
they do and to live maimed the do go into
the you know I've been extinguished five
years said it better than
expressions of approval become find
a great many leads. Point is
written that everyone shall be
fired and every victim stop so the devil
speaks to my children he did not produce
only desires to lead to below he is the
evil one whacks for no matter what name
introduces himself Lucifer
beautiful Mephistopheles.
No name. But it was a mistake
Oh yes he did not have
a Stop please my children lest you suffer
eternal damnation when he whispers in
your ear turn away your head and hearken
instead to the AIM do are no showed.
Me that Elena. You have if you live
right down be good do good but
Devon we do not want power over good man.
I am telling you right thing when you
current and terror are the devil. You are
sorry there are others
to your left as you and
a church. Lady.
I just come out to take yourself. As
a small brain and what knows
all the answers. Even
those who you lack. You know. When. I
know. I'm Fred I don't have to take you
back if you don't know too much. But don't
buy gas since you can't get trapped by no
good man got out of the coverage you know
my regen plainness. I ain't done
nothin around since you brought me
back. Eddie I've only been kind beast.
And I'm through it I wanted to go right
back in that man about my place to them
both. No lessons for me oh.
Man be so.
Far is not by any to be entered into
lightly but reverently discreetly and by
swiftly soberly and in the fear of God.
And of his holy estate these two persons
come now to be joined. If any man can
show just cause. Why they may not call it
a choice. But in the
house. Or else get off for
a. Charger wait
a minute. Please do it brought
up something quick. And I got to
speak now or like you sis.
Can't marry you. I do
too. And that's just what the
devil is working for you.
If you don't know how hard I've been trying
to help you in every way but afraid I
can't go much further than you not only
just trying yourself you just are needed
but I just can't stand it any longer. Let's
go on with the ceremony I'm like. My
eyes have been open Manua now would be the
worst thing I could do. It don't mean
that your last arc about like you said
this afternoon to be finding him again. To
be
a. Backyard with us. I
can only make you missed.
I think I do want to.
Come around like you.
Please to give.
It. We have
a visitor. You might
like to narrow that is
pressed pocket he's carrying that that he
got it with but you step two out. He's
been carrying it around ever since. In
similar cases. In our paper that you are
little that you would date the ghetto God.
That's what's known as poetic justice.
Not Mephistopheles much of the list
yourself the tone of the happenings. And
whispers in No you turn away. And to.
Your right and at the top of the.
Next shot. But I am never blood
no guy went to sleep. I wake.
Up so much the better swear.
I made him graduate to make it easy for
you. To make everything easy don't you.
Have a chore waiting for him up. I've
been a lot of new things. I go fix them
a drink. Make it feel like old times.
My day. My way out of commie I did.
As bracket I'm fixin
a couple of drinks. What's on your
mind well and I'm operating in St
Louis other spots. And I'm interested in
a couple of joints here East Bellamy steered
me to yield and you know that for sure
. I understand so as is my nature
to come to the point pronto
but your cats
a hundred grand and twenty five percent
of the take. To succeed hold on.
I may be from St Louis but I
ain't no HC you're operating
alone no prognosis are long I heard it was
Eddie Cagle head near outfit
Yeah but he's damn sure
a lot of narrow cuz I mean what I get
the flash since the cops found that it
already was your cat Yeah I really grew
up together I used to do his thinkin and
he did my fight and. Paid him off by putting
four slugs in them from his own right
like an attack is that you have
to blackmail this is smile he was
talking to who should know. Me.
You. Look like you seen
a ghost stop it and get out
I just shout out and them
a powerful as. My name is miles
away and. Places to meet you.
They call me judge. Maybe I can change.
Maybe I'm somebody else.
Somebody you know.
Now you can't be him. And. Who's him.
Take Medicaid off. You can't be this one
thing it's really maybe it ain't screwing
I don't just figure it out if I ain't
Judge Parker I might be somebody you know
maybe I'm that pal of yours Eddie Eddie
Cagle the one you're chopped down with it
don't ride. Figure and when you're afraid
of every shadow every footstep every
sound every dynamic your past every object
with. All of the gas hideout slowly.
Trying to figure it out E.K.G.
It always be
a laugh and when you can't take it
no more. Will Blow Your parade.
It is you know you've got to
turn the company. Great and I.
Was just. Under an addiction.
That.
You didn't shoot him we had a
bargain he was took care of
a better way and never even touched.
You go back to your hole in the ground
you're in my way I cannot go back without
you well know went to bed listening to
those school was able to escape from my
domain the school I've got to get you back
over to get it from derided by the people
who are big cataclysmic and proportion
Aleck. Looks like you got yourself behind
the eight ball come on eighty three he
has
a heart that has to take it up with the
boss and get my orders from him. On our
must die around of all of you again am I
doomed for the other to be vanquished
What is this human creature to be treated
in the recesses of this done to become
your favored. It was with evil intent that
he ventured forth he volunteered to do
my bidding lest I be humiliated by this
man could I demand my rights you're
missing the point. As
a number of call Judge Parker and the sweet
gal named Barbara what's been playing
good ball with
a lot of kids which might otherwise join
up with your team and me Eddie Cagle is
standing around to see that you
don't mess things up so long as
you remain in the Judge's body neither you
nor he can do anything once more you are
making Barbara very unhappy the longer
you remain on. The longer she cannot be
joined with our right for mate it was you
who got me in you were evil then I have
power over you thank you.
But I don't myself help you take me out
of his body. And the judge don't get
together like they should all
right I may give you if you lay off
the judge in Barbara for like.
Go back with you except I have to be ready
later I want to say goodbye to
perfect I cannot wait your wait lag.
A little farther I got to
see right away happen in
a car and come out oh yeah thanks Heidi.
So happy as and out as candidates.
I want to live is that we go to
dinner on
a show. I get so. Close. I'm
going to wait. I am. Assuming. I
would you be going away. At ten
years as friends on air standing.
On the understanding where you
go I want to go and. Pick up
a lot of our I'll go.
In on the game. And it.
Got everything except for YEAH ME So you
want to have no more trouble. I'm gone.
Jets can straighten everything
out. You want him get married.
And go on living it well.
It is.
Easy. To believe.
Kind of funny. Kind of busy guy
going to light it up yeah.
I guess what it is it it.
To my.
Am.
Planning.
And am.
Talking and please. Do not worry
this. Please try to reach in
some time to kind of just park is
a copy of. Your. Number
.
Two as in year. Six imagine.
He's fine now.
Funny. I never thought people's faces
look so good to. Have started things
I never noticed before. If I don't I know
the first trip around what I know now
when I get you down below I'm going to take
special pain to deal with I'm going to
introduce you to agonise and dreamed up man
and I thank you he spoke half an hour.
And you know Aren't you may just zap you.
You know I want you boys did you know
that. No big shot once it looked like
a sack. Fire was made at trustees to
share I'm blushing blackmail.
Or I don't know prat.